ZAKIAH BINTI MAT AHKHIR

Bachelor of Accountancy (Hons)

To whom it may concerns.

Dear Sir / Madam,

Application for job position

I am writing to explore the possibility of employment in your company. I am a degree holder from Uitm Arau Perlis in Bachelor of Accountancy (Hons). Currently, I am looking for a position that had been advertised by your company which is **account officer**. I have 2 years working experience as Account Assistant at audit firm

With my experience and educational background, I'm confident that my qualifications and skills could make significant contributing to your company. I will be able to operate computer especially Microsoft Office, Microsoft Excel and MYOB accounting system. I'm also know about GST Account and GST Coding. Besides that, I am a person who can work independently or as a part of team.

Enclosed is my resume, which shows in detail my educational and experience. I really hope that my qualifications be of interest to you and that the interview may be arranged.

Thank you for your consideration, I look forward to hear from you soon.

Sincerely,

Zakiah

Zakiah Bt Mat Ahkhir

Email: zakiahmatahkhir @ yahoo.com.my

H/P No.: 011-40728500

ZAKIAH BINTI MAT AHKHIR

4802 Kuala Muda,13110 Penaga, Seberang Perai Utara, Pulau Pinang 011-40728500 (H/P) 04-5793415 (Home) 890712-07-5236 zakiahmatahkhir@yahoo.com.my



Career Objective: To work in a company that given me an opportunity

to enhance my skills and knowledge which is useful

for me and my organization

Education and qualification:

Jan 2011 – Jan 2014 Bachelor of Accounting, Universiti Teknologi Mara,

Arau, Perlis (Current CGPA:3.11)

July 2007-Jun 2010 Diploma accountancy, Politeknik Seberang Perai

(CGPA 3.72)

Jan 2005-Dec 2006 SPM, Sekolah Menengah Teknik Butterworth, Pulau

Pinang

Working Experiences:

Jan 2015 – Current Arif & Associates, Kepala Batas (Account Assistant)

Prepare a full set of account Using MYOB system

Doing reconciliation bank

Prepare ageing for purchase and sales

Record transaction using general ledger

o Prepare schedule of asset and hire

purchase

April 2014 – Mei 2014 Imavathi & Co (Account Clerk)

 Prepare company transaction daily using Tally Accounting software

Handle petty cash, claims from staff and lawyer

• Prepare cheque for company activities

Feb 2013 – July 2013 Arif & Associates, Kepala Batas (Practical Training)

Prepare accounts for selected company using

MYOB

Prepare Audit Report for Dormant Company

Fill Taxation Form

Jan 2009-July 2009 Pertubuhan Peladang Kawasan Penaga (Practical

Training)

Responsible in Office fitting and documentation

 Data Processing and programming using SBKP System (Sistem Baja Padi Kerajaan Persekutuan)

Extra Curricular Activities:

Universiti Teknologi Mara

Participated in Tempur Tanpa Senjata Club (TTS)

• Member of MOBACC Accounting Club UiTM Arau, Perlis

Politeknik Seberang Perai

• Involves Product Innovation Competition

Sekolah Menengah Teknik Butterworth

- A committee of Netball Club
- A member of "Kadet Pertahanan Awam"
- Participated in consumer Quiz (Negeri Pulau Pinang)

Honors and Awards:

- A recipient for the Head of Commerce department awards (Semester 1, 2, 3, 5, 6) in Politeknik Seberang Perai
- Best attendance in Form 5 (2006)

Skills:

Computer: Able in Microsoft World excel and Microsoft PowerPoint,

Able to use in User Business System (UBS), Internet and

Networking, and Accounting System MYOB

Language: Proficient in Bahasa Melayu

Able to speak and write in English

Others:

Willingness to travel: Yes Willingness to relocate: Yes

References:

Pn Hasfiza Binti Hashim

Manager Arif Associates

No 17c, Tingkat2,

Jalan Dagangan 3,

Pusat Perniagaan Bertam,

13200 Kepala Batas,

En Mohamad Arif Bin Hj Musa

Director Arif & Associates

No 17c, Tingkat2,

Jalan Dagangan 3,

Pusat Perniagaan Bertam,

13200 Kepala Batas,

Pulau Pinang
Tel: 019-4334164
Pulau Pinang
Tel: 04 - 5754828